[dragon growls]
[Coco panting]
[Coco grunts]
[dragon growls]
[Coco panting]
- Isn't that...
- It is.
Richeh's hole again.
[RICHEH] How many times is that?
[TETIA] I've already lost count.
Come on, let's look
for a covered spot
where we can hide.
I think it's starting
to get colder.
♪
[dragon roars]
[Tetia whimpers]
[dragon continues roaring]
- [COCO] Um, Tetia.
- [TETIA] Huh?
Your hat.
You dropped it earlier.
Oh... Thank you, Coco.
[Tetia cries softly]
[COCO] So, are you all right?
No, how could you be?
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
[Tetia gasps]
No, I...
Wow, it's cold! You should wear
my cloak, Tetia,
I'll just snuggle up like this!
[TETIA] Uh...
Coco?
It's nice.
Whenever I put it on,
it makes me feel really safe.
♪
[COCO] No one would ever guess
that under that cloak,
I'm shaking with fear.
I know I look like a witch,
and that gives me
the strength to be brave.
With that in mind,
I want you to wear it now.
You'll be much more help
than I've been.
I'm sure.
[Tetia cries]
[Coco gasps]
- [Tetia crying]
- [COCO] What's happening?
What are they doing now?
[Coco gasps]
It's so warm.
A cloud? [gasps]
I'm sorry! I shouldn't have
looked at you
like you were
to blame for this!
[COCO] Huh?
Please, no.
You weren't wrong.
I am to blame.
And you didn't
say it out loud, so...
Saying it with my eyes
is no better.
The truth is,
I just got really scared,
and took it out on you.
You're the new girl.
I'm supposed to be the one
protecting you.
Tetia.
[Coco sniffles]
[COCO] You are protecting me!
This spell's so nice and warm,
I almost forgot
we were in danger!
Dragon? What dragon?
I'm taking a nap!
[Tetia laughs]
You know, I created this spell
all by myself.
Ever since I was little,
I've dreamed of napping
on a cloud.
So I've been
experimenting with it.
It's not finished yet, though.
When it is, I'd like to get it
approved for general use.
That way everyone will be
able to try it.
It's not a very useful spell,
but it's my dream,
and it's special to me.
This is your cloak,
so I want you to wear it.
Hold onto it until the day
we become real witches.
Then we can all take off
our novice cloaks together.
Fair?
[Coco chuckles softly]
[both laugh]
- [AGOTT] I heard all that.
- [both gasp]
[AGOTT]
If you want to lie on this,
it needs to be made from
a more substantive material.
- [RICHEH] Too cold outside.
- [both gasp]
[RICHEH] I'm coming in.
[AGOTT] And in order
to fly on it,
you'd need something light
yet durable,
like for instance, cotton.
That'd just be a normal,
boring mattress!
Dreams are all well and good,
but you can't escape reality.
We should discuss how
we're getting out of here, yes?
This whole area seems to be
under some manner of spell,
which is why
no matter where we go,
we end up back
in the same place.
And all magic,
even the forbidden kind,
requires a Casting Seal
in order to work.
We need to find out
where it is so that we can...
Uh?
I think I saw it!
Earlier.
[AGOTT] You're right.
There it is.
[RICHEH] Sure enough.
That's a Casting Seal.
Does, uh...
Does that dragon look like
it's gotten bigger?
Either that
or we're all getting smaller,
and so's the space.
Regardless, if the dragon
is protecting the Casting Seal,
we'll have to beat it.
- A bit of fire magic should--
- [COCO] Sorry, but!
Your last fire spell
didn't do that much damage.
- [AGOTT] Oh?
- Let me explain!
You slowed it down,
but I don't think
you actually hurt it,
which means...
We have to find something
it will respond to.
[Agott gasps]
Then, how do you propose
we beat it?
[COCO] We don't.
[ALL] Uh?
[ALL] Huh?
[Agott inhales deeply]
[AGOTT] What is this?
Are you still mad at me
about what I said before?
No, no, I'm not mad!
You and Tetia just gave me
an interesting idea.
[BOTH] Huh?
[COCO] I have a plan.
I don't know
if it'll work, but...
Let's try it.
♪
[scribbling]
[Tetia exclaims]
You mean it?
Yes!
We'll make Tetia's dream
a reality!
[Tetia exclaims]
What are you suggesting?
[COCO] Well, in Tetia's cloud,
we felt safe and warm
even in the bitter cold, right?
So, if we were to make
a cloud bed for the dragon,
it might get comfortable
and decide to stay there
instead of attacking us!
Really?
- Well, that sounds rather--
- Brilliant.
[RICHEH] None can withstand
the lure of a warm bed!
Not even dragons, probably!
Well said!
Uh, I don't know.
Give me a moment, please.
Let me think.
- Now...
- [Tetia giggles]
Humans love warm beds.
This we know.
[TETIA] Coco, are you all right?
[COCO] Me? Yes, I'm fine.
I was actually
wondering about
how the dragon
is doing right now.
[BOTH] Huh?
- The dragon?
- [COCO] Remember?
We were running away
from it, and then...
It slammed into a pillar,
really hard, nose-first.
At the time,
all I could think about
was how afraid I was.
But it must've hurt so much!
Now I feel bad
for the poor dragon.
[Agott sighs]
[COCO] And that's why
I like my plan.
So let's try!
I know it might not work,
but what do we have to lose?
Master told me something.
He said the spells which have
not been forbidden
are the ones that hold
the power to bring happiness.
So...
I want to show the dragon
some gentler magic.
If this does work,
that means no one
will have to get hurt.
Not any of us,
and not the dragon!
♪
[TETIA] Good point!
And if Agott decides
to help us,
then our chances of success
are even better, right?
Your eyes look like
you have an idea.
[AGOTT] Is that so?
Perhaps I do.
[TETIA] Right then,
let's work together.
You're the best of us
at drawing seals, after all.
That's obvious.
So with you on our team,
we can't lose!
[Agott inhales]
[exhales]
[AGOTT] Well...
Let's try it, then.
[COCO] Yay! [yelps]
[AGOTT] Watch out!
[Tetia sighs]
[COCO] Thank you, Agott!
[AGOTT] Never mind that!
Let's discuss our strategy!
[Tetia giggles] All right!
[AGOTT] You want to be able
to lie on it, correct?
[TETIA] Yes!
Just like a nice,
fluffy bed!
[AGOTT]
A material soft as a cloud,
- but with the necessary heft.
- [TETIA] Hmm...
Something we can find
in the area...
that would be able to withstand
the full weight of a dragon.
[gasps] Shredded paper!
No, our four Quires
wouldn't provide nearly enough.
- Our clothes!
- Our hair.
Still not enough.
And you don't want
to give those up, do you?
[Richeh and Coco grunt]
- [AGOTT] Sand, though.
- [ALL] Huh?
If only we... [gasps]
The Wall Breaker spell!
We can create a fine sand
by demolishing
the walls and floors.
[TETIA] That's perfect!
Who doesn't enjoy lying around
on a sandy beach?
Smart thought, Agott!
[AGOTT] And the more signs
drawn to the seal,
the finer the sand.
Especially with smaller seals.
If it's tiny seals you need,
then just leave it to me!
Look at the speed!
This is Richeh's specialty!
Tetia, from you,
I'll need a spell
to gather the sand in the plaza
without packing it too hard.
I'll get to work
on an enveloping spell
that will keep it in place.
Yes, ma'am!
- [COCO] Um, Agott?
- [AGOTT] Huh?
Is there anything I can do?
[AGOTT] There isn't, no.
I have agreed to your plan,
but at your current skill level,
I can't trust you to help
with the magic.
You'd do well
to stay out of our way.
[Coco gasps softly]
[COCO] Such a perfect circle.
How does she do it?
[COCO] She practices the circle
in the air a few times,
then starts at the point
closest to her.
Do Tetia and Richeh
use that technique as well?
[COCO]
And how have I been doing it?
Where to start...
The final shape...
I guess I never thought
about those things.
I'll try it.
And until...
I can do it like they can.
♪
I'll keep trying!
Like this... Right?
Then this...
[dragon roaring]
[roaring continues]
[Richeh breathing shakily]
It's cold.
Yes, and it's gotten dark.
Shall I start a fire?
[RICHEH] I'm all out of paper.
- [TETIA] So am I.
- [Agott groans]
[AGOTT] No, it won't work.
A Sign of Convergence
would pack it too hard.
What if you wrap it
in a membrane of air?
[AGOTT] Too weak.
It would fall apart.
[Tetia groans]
[RICHEH] Reinforce it
with fine strips of cloth, then.
[AGOTT] I'm afraid that won't be
enough to make a difference.
And it's going to get
even colder, so...
[RICHEH] Never mind.
[Tetia groans] Come on,
there has to be something.
- [Agott sighs]
- [TETIA] What to do, what to do.
[AGOTT] There must be a way.
Some perfect plan.
[Coco gasps]
I...
I did it!
[both gasp softly]
Ah, brilliant.
- But how exactly does--
- Completely stable.
She cast a Pyreball!
Yours used to fizzle right out!
When did you learn
to cast it so well?
Now. I just watched all of you,
and then I practiced,
over and over.
I kept trying, till finally...
[Tetia exclaims]
How wonderful!
You really did it, Coco!
Please...
Given enough time
and repetition,
anyone would be able to...
Enough repetition?
[Agott gasps]
That's it! I've got it!
[all gasp]
♪
[AGOTT] Are we ready?
- [COCO] Hm.
- You just say the word.
[Agott inhales deeply]
[AGOTT] Let's go!
♪
[TETIA] Coco!
[COCO] Thank you!
[AGOTT]
It's definitely grown larger.
- We must finish this quickly!
- [dragon growls]
- [AGOTT] Richeh, go!
- [RICHEH] Right.
[Coco panting]
♪
[gasps softly] Done. Coco!
It's time.
- Signal to close the rings.
- [RICHEH] Hm.
- [RICHEH] Three...
- [COCO] Two...
[COCO AND RICHEH] One.
[AGOTT] Next station.
[dragon growling]
[dragon roars]
- [COCO] It noticed!
- [TETIA] We need to meet up!
[AGOTT] You finished your rings?
[RICHEH] And activated them.
- Good. [pants]
- [TETIA] Repetition?
[AGOTT] Yes.
In order to prevent
the spell from falling apart,
we'll wrap it
in repetition magic
that constantly returns it
to its initial form.
That is...
by enveloping the Wall Breaker
and Billow Cluster combination
within a Repetition Spell,
we'll create a cloud of sand.
Based upon the size
of the dragon,
I should think we'll need five.
If we can properly synchronize
the positioning and timing
to combine five into one,
even if it sinks
with the beast's weight,
the sand cloud will keep
returning to its original shape,
and maintain
the same downy quality.
[BOTH] It's called...
[dragon roars]
[BOTH]
The Dragon Disabler Duvet!
Actually, it's the
Serpent's Bed of Sand.
Another smart thought
from Agott!
- Agott to agree.
- [AGOTT] Enough silliness!
This is our chance
to get past it!
[dragon snores]
- [COCO] Tetia?
- [TETIA] Hm?
- [COCO] Something wrong?
- [Tetia chuckles]
[TETIA] Nothing at all.
I just couldn't help but look.
That dragon looks really happy
right now, doesn't it?
You know,
I think this is the first time
my magic has ever made
someone happy.
[Coco chuckles softly]
[Tetia chuckles softly]
I never knew it could make me
so happy as well!
[dragon growling]
- [AGOTT] Well...
- [COCO] Yes.
This must be it.
What kind of spell is it?
No kind that I've seen.
[AGOTT] Hm...
- I imagine Master might know.
- [Qifrey panting]
[brushbuddy sniffs]
[brushbuddy squeaks]
[QIFREY] Did they come this way?
[brushbuddy squeaks, sniffs]
No trace of them.
Did they move on already?
[TARTAH] Wait.
Wasn't this alley paved?
I remember flagstones here.
Guess they were removed
at some point.
[Qifrey gasps]
[QIFREY] Brushbuddies are drawn
to the smell of Conjuring Ink.
[gasps] Is this...
[Tartah grunts]
[QIFREY] Get back!
[all screaming]
[AGOTT] How could you have
broken the seal
so spontaneously?
What were you thinking?
[TETIA] I was thinking we needed
to break the seal!
[COCO] Everyone, look up there!
I can see the sky!
- A way out! It has to be!
- [dragon growls]
[AGOTT] Coco, get down!
[screaming]
[COCO] Ago...
[AGOTT] Oh, no!
Without my Sylph Shoes...
I'm in a spot of trouble here.
[dragon growls]
[Agott grunts, gasps]
[AGOTT] Master?
A dragon, well...
- [AGOTT] Master, I...
- Not now. It's coming.
[dragon growling]
Hold on tight.
I need my hands free.
[AGOTT] Right!
♪
[dragon growling]
[Qifrey sighs]
You should be safe now.
It appears to be unconscious.
- Agott?
- [gasps] Oh, sorry?
[Tetia cries] Master!
- You came to save us, thank you!
- [QIFREY] Tetia! Richeh!
How were you able
to get here, Master?
I was trying to find all of you,
and the space suddenly
opened up around me.
[Qifrey gasps softly]
[QIFREY] Where's Coco?
♪
[WITCH] Greetings, Coco.
So long have I waited
for the seed I planted
to finally sprout.
Were you pleased with
the assignment I gave you?
Did it help you in your growth?
Ah, yes!
I have a gift for you.
I'll teach you
all sorts of things
Qifrey never could.
And when the time comes...
Ah... what a day
it shall be!
[TETIA] Coco! Coco!
[TETIA] Coco!
[Coco groans]
[Tetia exclaims]
[COCO]
Master Qifrey, everyone...
- [gasps] Where's Agott--
- I'm here.
[AGOTT]
Thank you for this, Tartah.
Oh, it's nothing.
I'll see if I can get
Grandad to come by.
- Thank goodness.
- [footsteps]
Are we in Kalhn?
[TETIA] Yes, we made it back
safe and sound!
[QIFREY] It's fortunate
I found you.
You were unconscious
on the tower stairs.
[COCO] The stairs?
Wait. Your memory.
Did the Brimmed Caps
do something to you?
No! I think I just need
to regain my bearings.
That's all.
[Coco gasps]
- [TETIA] Coco?
- [COCO] Huh?
Are you all right?
[gasps] Yes. I'm perfectly fine
now that I...
[Coco cries]
[Coco cries] I'm so sorry.
I put all of you in danger.
I'm really, really sorry.
[QIFREY] Tetia filled me in
on how you found
yourselves there.
The actions you took.
All of it.
[Coco breathes shakily]
[QIFREY] It sounds to me
as though you saved everyone.
[Coco gasps]
You see, in magic,
the idea behind a spell
is as important as
one's penmanship.
Let's work hard
to nurture that talent.
[Coco breathes shakily]
[Coco whimpers]
[Coco chuckles softly]
Right!
Oh, Coco! I'm so relieved
that you're safe!
[COCO] I'm sorry
for worrying you!
You too, Richeh and Agott.
[Nolnoa laughs]
[NOLNOA] Not only safe,
but full of energy!
[QIFREY] Indeed,
thanks to your help.
The hour has grown quite late.
If I may, I would suggest
you stay at an inn tonight--
[QIFREY] Mr. Nolnoa.
I have a favor
I must ask of you.
[NOLNOA] Oh?
[QIFREY] There's a Casting Seal
drawn on the back of this.
It would be very helpful to me
if I could know what the ink
was made from.
Would you investigate?
[NOLNOA] I see. The ink, eh?
[QIFREY] And please, do not tell
the Knights Moralis about this.
[gasps] Come now!
We have a duty, you know!
Forbidden Magic
sightings must be... Uh?
You will tell no one.
Not a soul.
[high-pitched ringing]
[Nolnoa gasps]
[Nolnoa sighs]
[NOLNOA] My...
Just what is happening here?
[TARTAH] Uh?
Over there. Isn't that yours?
[NOLNOA] Or rather,
what's about to happen...
I wonder.